{"test_questions": [[{"question": "A half-moon protractor is divided into how many degrees?", "opta": "360", "optb": "180", "optc": "270", "optd": "310", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A line drawn with a long section, short dash, and another long section is a ________.", "opta": "hidden feature", "optb": "center of a circle", "optc": "center axis of a hidden cylinder", "optd": "center of a radius", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Traditional drafters need to be able to create several different line widths because ________.", "opta": "different line widths convey different information", "optb": "the line width has to do with how dark it appear in the finished drawing", "optc": "they seem to transmit better in a fax machine", "optd": "it makes no difference", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Several of the tools used in traditional drafting include the following:", "opta": "Parallel straight edge", "optb": "45 degree triangle", "optc": "Circle template", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A civil engineer working on a bridge design would probably rely on his ________ scale for checking printed drawings.", "opta": "engineer's", "optb": "metric", "optc": "architect's", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In order to convert fractional inches into decimal inches ________.", "opta": "look on a metric conversion chart", "optb": "divide the numerator (top number) by the denominator (bottom number)", "optc": "check the engineer's scale", "optd": "all of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An engineer's scale would be used to measure lines on a drawing where the scale factor reads ________.", "opta": "1/4\" = 1'-0\"", "optb": "1/8\" = 1'-0\"", "optc": "1\" = 100'", "optd": "3/4\" = 1'-0\"", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Referring to the fractional inches to decimal inches to millimeter conversion chart on page 55 what is the equivalent mm measurement of 3/16 inch.", "opta": "1.906", "optb": "4.7625", "optc": "5.958", "optd": "14.6844", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Some traditional board drafters preferred the drafting machine over the parallel straight edge because it could be used without the need for________.", "opta": "circle templates", "optb": "triangles", "optc": "technical pens", "optd": "lettering guides", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The first step in creating a traditional technical drawing is to ________.", "opta": "draw a series of guide lines", "optb": "set up the miter line", "optc": "align the paper so that it will be positioned square to the parallel bar", "optd": "sharpen the leads in the technical pens", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}